Remember, none of that sneaky crap. Got it?
About time. Though you didn't make it easy.
Yeah, that was real rude. I found them nearby like you said. Oh yeah, I figured you'd want me to bring her too.
Face it, you lost and now you're all out of tricks.
No. Why are you here?
Well, isn't this sweet? A nice family reunion. Now get over here.
I see. If that's your choice, then so be it.
No!
I have something I want to ask first. The photo. Who gave it to Lu Guang that night? Was it you?
What photo are you talking about? The kid was at the hospital, but he was helping me. You wrote the hand off, right?
It's just you. So what's up? Are you my new babysitter?
Ha! Well, then I'm telling you right now. I don't need you here.
Okay, what's that supposed to mean?
Oh, I see. Damn, that is good. Really thinking ahead.
Ha! You take care of that now.
Creepy little ninja almost got his nose.
Really? I thought you were looking for your sister.
Why would I lie to you?
I don't know. Why would you?
It was you. Your sister told us.
I thought it... might change the past.
The truth comes out. Must everyone betray me? Hand over the phone.
Hang on, boss. Why are you acting all surprised about this?
You knew. I told you. That night at the station. Why are you calling him out now?
He should have handed it over. Not doing it just proves he's got a motive.
What? Oh! You already figured that out, didn't you?
Idiot. Such a waste. Though I did like your obedience.
Sadly, you never knew when to shut up.
And now everyone knows too much.
You knew this whole time.
You played ignorant so you could keep using me.
He never trusted you to start with.
Shut up! I was clear! I cannot abide betrayal! I won't! Ever!
And yet you still did it!
From the beginning, all we've ever done was use each other.
You can't betray that.
How can you say that to me?
I took care of you, raised you and your mute sister like you were my own!
That's crap! You didn't raise them like family. Just your tools!
You don't get to judge me! You don't know anything about my life!
But then, none of it matters anyway. Not really.
You can go back. Fix it all. Take it. Make a world where none of this had to happen.
This is all because of her. She's the mistake that needs to be fixed! Now do it!
Now do it!
What happened here? Did a gas pipe explode?
I don't know. Someone called the fire department.
I'm on the phone with them now.
You don't need to get back up.
You're gonna need backup...
You're gonna need backup!
I'm gonna need backup!
I need backup!
I took my phone!
Police. Everyone get back and stay out of the way!
Get out of here, Bass.
Thank goodness you're right.
Hey, you okay?
Where are the others?
It happened so fast.
I thought we were almost free.
And everything collapsed around us.
We were knocked out for a moment.
Once we came to, we started helping who we could.
Shang-Chi-Shan?
Where is he?
Are people still in the theater?
They need to get in there.
Someone knocked me out.
They took him and Li Tianxi.
I don't know where,
but they couldn't have gotten far.
Not with all this.
Police would be all over the area soon.
They'll put this place on lockdown.
No one's getting in or out without being checked.
Right.
Then why would they set off the explosion in the first place?
Unless, we already had some other way to escape.
They had me somewhere underground.
I know because I heard the subway.
If they had access, they could run.
Possibly.
It's midnight.
So the subways won't be running.
Or which line?
Cao Hua.
In the warehouse,
there were boxes from a bakery at Cao Hua Station.
That's close.
But that line runs north and south.
Then we'll split up.
Fine.
Stay safe.
And stay smart.
I'm not asking for much here.
Just go back and stop her from meeting Zhuang Shuai.
Why is that more important than stopping her murder?
He thought she betrayed him.
So he killed her.
Bullshit!
I saw what they were doing behind my back.
They barely hid it!
You also asked me to kill him.
Or did you forget?
When my sister and I worked together,
I can do a lot more than just control someone.
I can look into their memories.
You were so convinced of their betrayal
that you never asked me what I saw.
I saw them rehearse,
eat,
talk,
and perform.
That was all.
No one's coming to see the play.
I'm worried.
The theater might close down.
It sucks.
But there's not much we can do about it.
Theater's costly.
Not everyone can afford it.
We barely charge for tickets, though.
Maybe it's the subway noise?
Oh, hey.
Are you free tonight?
I found a new venue.
And it might be cheaper.
Unfortunately, no.
But why show it at night?
That's kind of weird.
You can go.
It's not like we're the boss or anything.
It's an office space right now.
They haven't officially put it on the market.
We'd have to wait for the tenants to clear out.
My husband hates it when I come home late.
A perk of his job.
Always worried.
Or he just loves you.
Well, you can see the design of this place doesn't work as an office.
But for a theater, it's great.
You could make it so unique.
Excuse me.
I'll be one second.
Hey.
What's up?
You're at home?
I thought you were still at work.
No.
We closed the case.
And why are you still out?
Oh, I'm checking out a new venue.
This late?
All by yourself?
I'm not alone.
Da Shui is here.
It's fine.
Who is that?
Right.
We were in my last play together.
You'll meet him.
But for right now, we're busy.
See you soon.
Sorry for that.
Let's continue.
Every day they were on that stage.
Being so intimate.
All those rehearsals and late night dinners.
They were always together.
How could it be innocent?
How is she not betraying me?
She lied.
I never make mistakes.
There's no way I was wrong.
They know what they did to me.
They got what they deserved.
You are insane.
What are you talking about?
I can still fit into it.
Sure, I gained a few pounds after the wedding.
But a little dieting will fix that.
And your child too?
Shut up!
You don't get to say that!
I won't be judged by some monster!
That's what you all are!
You're all nothing more than goddamn monsters!
Fuck!
Oh!
Yes!
Ah!
You asshole!
You had a vest this whole time?
And you had me out there risking my neck?
Then you tried to kill me!
Well, who's dead now, huh?
Don't you run from me, arrogant suit-wearing prick!
Get back here, coward!
It's only fair I get to shoot you two!
It's only fair!
Why are you helping him?
He risked a lot coming to us for help.
We still can, but you have to trust us!
Why the hell for?
I tried all that.
I gave you the photo, but nothing has changed.
We're still stuck living in this hell.
You did nothing.
Just like everyone else.
All right.
Go and get the picture.
I should be trying to save her, not a damn picture!
The cost is too great.
Without that photo, our present is gone.
Ever since that day, I haven't had a future!
I haven't had a future!
Indeed, I haven't had to shoot her.
I haven't had to pay the wat for her.
I don't know.
I haven't had to shoot in line!
Maybe then?
Do not have enough potential to shoot her now.
But I am here!
Let's善...
I can't wait...
Let me burn...
...
But not anymore.
I'm gonna rewrite destiny.
Lupin, watch out!
Let him go!
What would you do to save him?
Huh?
Isn't he your best friend?
If I killed him right now, what would you do?
What would you do to fix it?
Kill me?
Or go back and change EVERYTHING?
Huh?
I...
Wanna...
Go...
Help!
Here, this part means I.
And this means want.
And...
That was the sign for to return.
Make a triangle with your fingers.
Then bring it up all the way here.
And that means home.
You Themysk
toning
Ya